See you
next
time.
What's going on?
How did you get here in the first place?
This is dangerous, you know.
What are you...
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Sniper King, the King of the Snipers.
To make a long story short,
I've come to rescue you.
You're really serious.
I'm not alone, of course.
Your friend Sanji and a
cyborg thug named Franky
are currently engaged
in battle on this train.
They kept the enemy busy long
enough for me to come here.
Furthermore,
Captain Luffy and the
rest of the Straw Hats
are following closely on another C-train.
I hear he's bringing
a small army with him.
On my way here, I peeked inside
the other train cars. Frankly,
I believe the four agents in the car
behind us may prove too great a challenge.
If possible, I would like to escape
with you before Sanji has to face them.
Come.
Let's run away. Together.
What's the matter?
There's no need to worry.
I've made all of the
necessary preparations.
Here.
These octo-shoes are for you.
If you use them on your hands and feet,
you can climb through the window and
stick to the outer panels of the C-train.
Quickly, put them on before they notice.
I won't go. Why not?
I don't know why you're doing this.
I told you very clearly that
I wouldn't see you again.
I said that I would never
return to the Straw Hats.
The situation has changed.
They know why you turned yourself in.
That ice gentleman from the
shipyard clarified everything.
So he survived after all?
But still, that doesn't change my mind.
I won't go with you no matter what.
Enough with that already.
Don't you get it?
They aren't so weak that they
need you to worry about them.
What were you thinking?
Accepting such a stupid deal before
talking to the rest of the crew?
You think they'd be happy to go on?
Knowing that one of their friends
had thrown her life away for them?
Now that they know why you left,
they'll follow you to the
depths of hell if they have to.
And they'll bust every skull
they can on the way there.
You don't get it, do you?
That's the kind of guy Luffy is.
How many times do I have to tell you this?
Even if you think you can save
me, I don't want your help.
Don't you care how I feel?
Come on, give me a break.
Hey, keep it down in there, you.
What's the matter?
Now that we're getting
close to Eni's lobby,
is that cool exterior of yours
finally starting to melt away?
Well, you can cry all you like,
but there's no point in lamenting your
fate after it's already been sealed.
Really, I'm fine.
Strange.
That's not the reaction I was expecting.
I can't put my finger on it, but
there's something different about her.
Maybe it's just my imagination.
I said I'm fine.
Now, please, just leave me alone.
This is definitely fishy.
Why is she goofing off
at a time like this?
Ravideers?
I'd like to welcome you to the
wonderful world of ramen Kenpo!
That is the lamest power-up ever.
Go, go, go!
Here I come!
Ramen Gin Po!
Pork punch fake attack!
That's the same useless punch
from before, only bigger.
Ah, damn it!
I'm stuck in this stupid thing!
Go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
So what do you think?
My ramen Cape attacks are
pretty impressive, aren't they?
It's kind of hard to look cool when your
arm and leg are buried
in noodles like that.
And now I believe it's time to pay you back
for all those kits you gave me earlier.
What the hell are you
getting dizzy for, you idiot?
You were trying to make me woozy using
your freaky eyebrows again, weren't you?
Bad move!
You're gonna pay for that!
Ah, dammit!
It's impossible to fight back like this!
Here comes my noodle soul press!
Once a more! Kiss!
Another helping!
Another helping! Another
helping!
Finally, I'm afraid.
Go, go, go!
That's what you get for
underestimating me, you Moon!
No one stands a chance against
my madman, Ramen Kenpo!
If I attack him, I'm going to get
caught in those noodles again.
I'll just have to avoid
that stupid suit of his.
Go, go, go!
Have a taste of this!
Ramen and Kyoza combo!
Clappy!
And that leaves me only one place
where I can attack this annoying clown.
Escalo!
Run at me!
As you can see, I don't have a weak spot.
And I've already figured
out your fighting style.
Every one of your attacks
is some form of kicking.
So if I lock down your
legs, you're finished.
Go, go, go, go!
Sucks to be you, huh?
No matter what you do, you'll still
end up getting stuck in my soup.
Now, Mr.
Wet Noodle, while we're at
it, try this one on for size!
Ramen Kenpo!
Multi-noodles, please!
What the heck did you do to my noodles?!
I turned that hunk of pasta
fettolini into a platter.
Huh?
Some sort of trick?
Hey!
You sloshed my noodle
fist to shreds, you jerk!
A chef must fight without using his
hands or knives. Those are sacred.
So it's always been my policy
to not use them in battle.
But since we're in a kitchen,
And you're using food as a weapon that
changes things a bit now, doesn't it?
Well, I knew you were a pain in the
butt, but that one really takes the cake.
Thousand noodles!
Trying to look cool, you
instant little punk, huh?
An amateur cook like you shouldn't
even touch my precious kitchen knives,
you hear me?
Those are meant for
trained professionals only!
Say I sincerely apologize for
my insolence in your kitchen,
but I'm going to let you in
on a little culinary secret?
It's time for a demonstration!
This is how a real chef gracefully
handles his kitchen knives.
I'm hammered!
Paper art.
How about a taste of fresh fire?
Has this guy lost his mind?
He jumped out over the sea!
Moonwalk!
How in the hell did this freak
jump back in midair like that?
Why doesn't my tempest kick
have any effect on him?
There's something strange about his body.
I've had enough of you! Likewise!
What the hell are you?
Are we there yet?
Where's Bashin' Tom?
It's Puffin' Tom.
Anyway, get inside
before you catch a cold.
You just changed clothes and
you're soaking wet already.
I don't care.
It's more awesome up here. Fine.
Now, Gum-Gum!
300-caliber cannon!
Boom!
Whoa!
Would all of you stop screwing around?
We're bored.
Polish your weapons or something.
What's wrong with you?
Uh, yeah.
I tried to tell those guys the same thing
earlier, but they wouldn't listen to me.
Hey, check it out!
There's a train in front of us!
It's the Puffing Tom!
Seems a bit early, don't you think?
Damn it.
What's going to happen to us now?
There's no engine on this car.
All we can do is wait it out.
Ah! Another way!
Oh, this storm is still pretty bad.
You think someone will come save us?
Hey, guys!
There's something approaching from behind.
Really?
It must be a rescue ship.
I don't think so.
Actually, it looks like
it's coming on the railway.
There's no way.
There's only one Sea Train in the
world, and we're on it right now.
Besides, it's Aqua Laguna.
No one could make it out
of Water 7 in this weather.
Well, if it's not a train, then...
What the heck is it?
That's the buffing tom, all right.
But it's just a caboose.
There's no engine.
And it doesn't look like it's moving.
That can't be right.
What's going on here?
Does this mean it got detached somehow?
Huh!
Maybe something happened and
Sandy and Usopp were on there.
Big bro Franky, too!
Well, I hope not, because
we're about to crash into him!
Granny, hit the brake!
I already told you now, didn't I?
We don't got one.
We're gonna crash!
Luffy, what are you gonna do?
I'm flying over to see what's up.
Now, come, go!
Rockets!
Whoa!
There's something in the sky!
What happened?
Ow, ow, ow!
All right, I made it!
Who the hell is this weirdo? Hello? Saji?
Are you in here?
Poor Usopp.
Hey, Saji!
You hear me?
It's maybe over there.
Wait a sec.
I know that face.
It's Straw Hat Luffy!
Hello!
Are you there, Saji?
I can't hear you!
Shut up!
Bring it on!
We're not scared of you!
Where's Sanji? Wait, what?
I don't know who that is!
Sanji! He's my friend!
Sorry, never heard of him!
Too bad. See ya!
Shoot him!
Strawhead's coming out!
Looks like they're shooting
him, and he's saying no!
Well, whatever happened, the train
cars must be full of marines.
Well, what's the plan, boatman?
If we don't move those cars out of
the way, we might get knocked off!
Holy crap, it is a Sea Train after all.
They're going to ram right into us.
Yeah, and if they don't slow down soon,
we're going to get smashed to pieces.
Let the Franky family handle this.
We'll dismantle them
before they can hit us.
What may help?
I want to break stuff too.
Hear that, men?
Get to work. Yeah!
Hey!
Roronoa!
Hear that, Roronoa?
He's calling for you.
Go ahead! Cut him!
Okay.
That's it!
The ego of the entropic world
shall be rent in twain.
Two-sword style, sword draw.
Rashomon!
Warpah!
Hey, if you're gonna do something crazy
like that, you gotta warn us first.
You heard me say cut him, didn't you?
But I didn't think he
could actually do it.
Of course he could do it.
We'd be dead right now if you couldn't.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
But you're gonna give me a heart attack.
He's got all that power?
And he's not even the leader of the crew?
We're not done yet.
What the hell is that?
It's a Sea King!
There's someone waiting on this railway.
I...
someone who can cut Sea Kings in half.
Everyone get back to the
front cars right now!
This is a trap!
What are you talking about?
What the...
How foolish to fall
for the enemy's scheme!
Have a safe trip, gentlemen.
Say hello to the Sea Kings for me.
I must catch the train.
I must rectify my mistake
and capture the prisoners
before their evil is once
again set upon this world.
I cannot allow the blood and tears
of innocent civilians to be shed.
I'll show them that there's justice
yet In this cruel and unforgiving world
I don't care if my body is stored or
stranded by these raging waves I swear,
no matter the cost I protect the future
of law-abiding citizens everywhere
No, it can't be.
It seems there's another Sea Train, huh?
I see someone.
What the?
Hey!
There's a guy out there!
It's the Ship Slasher!
That's not good!
Ship what?
They call him Ship Slasher T-Bone!
He's from the Navy!
His sword cuts through pirate ships
like a knife cuts through a stake!
Whoa!
That sounds awesome!
Maybe it'd be awesome if it
was somebody else's problem.
All right, men, let's go.
We only get one shot.
Set your sights on
T-Bone! You ready? Yeah!
Hold on!
What?
We don't have time to hold on!
He's gonna cut Rocketman in half!
Geez, there's nothing to worry about!
Zorro's got this! Just watch!
I'm only gonna tell you this one time!
Get the hell out of the way!
There's no other track.
I'm sure they passed by
my men on the way here.
What did those monsters do to them?
They must be Nico Robin's crewmates!
In that case that swordsman is the pirate
hunter those who defile this path of
justice will face my wrath i am a proud
captain of the navy i shall not let you
pass be it wood or steel i'll slash your
ship in two good luck with that one we
won't stop until we reach our goal and i'll
cut down We've got anything in our way!
This guy is fierce.
Angar!
I hate cooking sword blades!
Right angle, right bird!
Three sword style.
Bull demon.
He cut right through it.
Bold hoops.
He beat Demo!
He must have come from
one of the loose cars.
Gotta hand it to him.
It takes a lot of guts to keep
going in a storm like this.
But still, that's not enough to stop us.
I'm sure the burden of
justice is a heavy one.
But we've got a few burdens of our own.
Hurry! Hurry!
Captain T-Bone is out here!
He needs our help!
What if he already got
hit by that C-Train?
Hey, don't even joke about
something like that, you bastard!
Our captain would cut that crappy
train in two and you'll know it!
You think it was Sanji?
Of course, how else do you think those
train cars got detached good strategy, huh?
So you think we'll catch
up soon seems like it